he's a terrorist but um
well as you heard my name is my hair
it's unbelievable
the full name is actually
isn't that nice thank you
in arabic maher means skill
in english maher means airport security
is what it means
with the extended arab stairs just
airport security you should see my dad
at the airport nervous
nelly he's very arab he's essentially a
camel
and
you should see him he asks questions
arabs shouldn't ask at the airport you
know
this is a very big plane yes
he makes wings
what's wrong with you
he's a terrorist but um
no i think he is
i was born in lebanon give it up for
hummus
we eat that at costco um
where's the sam's out here i guess
whatever it doesn't matter it's not
promoted by either one of them so
i was raised however where all arabs are
raised
uh the deep south
that was fine my fourth day of high
school
this guy comes up to me he goes hey
look here jose
you need to get your butt back to mexico
where you belong
i said look pal i'm from the middle east
he goes what do you mean like saint paul
minneapolis
i said that's the midwest
[Laughter]
he goes what do you mean then i said you
know man lebanon
jordan where they filmed aladdin
he goes oh you're one of them a-ramps
kind of whispered it i don't know why
you wanted to make your wraps well look
here muhammad
you need to get back to mexico where you
alone
so i moved to mexico but
my wife she's not here tonight she's
at home cooking and cleaning for me
oh no no she's
she's in the car but there's
no that's terribly racist no she's
no she's dead but the thing is
no she's no she's a terrorist but the
thing is i
can't no
she's not she is but
my wife is actually you didn't think you
would come and laugh with the word
terrorist right
so funny my wife is actually uh
italian-american and i
am arab american we have the hairiest
children you have ever seen
we have squirrels at home seriously
my son's hairline
starts like
it's just he just he just has two big
eyebrows to just come
up i've never seen his face he's five
it's just
we uh we debated
two names for my son paul
and mustafa brahman and which was
we chose paul we don't want to send that
to kindergarten could you imagine where
i grew up something to kindergarten
could you imagine just everybody okay
everybody listen up
got a new student this is
mustafa abdulrahman
am i saying that right does does he need
a prayer rug or how does that work i
don't know
can somebody vacuum the bus say let's
hair everywhere
is he a werewolf or
paul my oldest he's cute he's you know
what's happening he sucks his thumb i
can't get him to stop
tried everything time out taking away
toys i've tried everything
now i'm on this new thing for him uh
hookah and
no it's great he's loving it i love it
giving me some hookah he's so
cute and he's not stuck in his thumb now
so it's amazing
but he smells like double apples so it's
kind of
strawberries following us kind of nice
paul my oldest i think is
now he is he is uh
five or 26 but he's
he doesn't like to sleep typical
lebanese guy likes to go out
go to clubs you know that kind of
lebanese guy and so
he doesn't like to sleep the only time
paul sleeps is in a moving vehicle
you know i'm talking about people little
kids they go to sleep in the car boom
they're out
so now what does dad do at 7 45
i get him an uber and uh
[Music]
i send him out for nine hours and it's
just
amazing the baby the little one sleeps
fine we don't hear him at all
in the garage and
[Music]
that's good
so this is when it gets kind of sad um i
started losing my hair uh very early
like 7 a.m
no i was 15. yeah
yeah yeah yeah it's sad 15 and in high
school i was esl and
ibs
two terrible acronyms to have
simultaneously
i started losing my hair early man 15 t
my mom took me to the doctor
and she goes this is what she said she
goes doctor
fix him
[Laughter]
so he gave me rogaine
yeah 15 years old really just a special
year it was
i ran home with the road game like
charlie and the chocolate factory i was
so excited
took it home you shake it up you have to
shake it first it says
like you're not embarrassed enough
you've got to shake this stuff so you
guys shake this stuff and you spray it
i spray it on and folks it worked
miracles on my back and shoulders
because now
i'm essentially a thin brown bear is
what i am
like an out of shape bear like a very
skinny bear
and i wanted to play high school
basketball when i was a kid freshman
year in high school i wanted to try out
so i showed up to the tryouts right and
the coach inevitably of course
he says okay boys here's what it won't
shirts against skins
so i said please just whatever happens i
don't even want to make the team just
please
do not let me be a skin and sure enough
it's one of these things where he's
going
sure skin he's just picking it random
sure enough shirts
he comes close to me sure it's good
like slow motion scoot
i peed from the ibs i was so nervous
it's good land's right on me so i said
forget i don't care whatever i want to
play basketball so i reach over i take
my shirt off
but i did it kind of dramatically like i
didn't care you know i was like
just threw it off there immediately the
theme song to lion king came on it was
just
a rhino ran across the room it was
ridiculous
and the coach without missing a beat he
goes okay billy you go over there thomas
you go over there and my hair let me get
you uh
oh wow uh is he the mascot or what's
going on here i don't know
i made the team though believe it or not
bald and like had the u-shape you know
like
the years going on i had an accent that
was so cute in high school
just full of popularity
will you go to the dance with me
we take my father's taxi
that was inappropriate but um
should have been an uber but the thing
is
i got married in mexico and my best man
you think i'm harry
my best man he's this lebanese guy
and his suit was so tight he was you
know he's living these guys that got
like
the nightclubs and their suit was so his
suit is so tight you've seen these guys
with the chest hairs coming up
over the shirt have you seen these guys
he's my best man
okay we're exchanging vows i look over
but roger's chest hair is coming up
over the shirt it's getting in his face
it's like
[Laughter]
it's it's moving like seaweed it's like
[Music]
it's like waving at people like
anyway he's dead now but um
now here's the thing i do um speak
arabic
and after comedy shows people say like
hey man that's great you speak
let me just ask how do you say my name
in arabic people say all the time how do
you say my name in arabic
last week at a comedy show this guy was
like hey man how do you say my name
and i said what is it he goes gary i was
like i don't know
we don't have it i'm sorry your name is
because we don't have gary now here's
what happened okay
for probably nine months
this guy at work called me samir
i had enough it was just one of those
things like i let it slide for a while
he's like hey samira can you help me i
was like that's
it this is ridiculous it's my hair i'm
gonna go tell him i've had enough
so i walked up to him and i said hey um
dave can we talk and he goes sure sure
but it's john
[Laughter]
oh never mind
a very awkward experience
hi he's a terrorist too but i um no he's
not that was last reference i promise
yeah so i used to you're gonna love this
ready for this one
i uh i used to be a state trooper
yeah yeah cool i was the worst
state trooper you ever seen and you're
you know why
because i would stop a car and then i'd
forget why i stopped it
it was weird i was just thinking about
other stuff let's pretend this is a car
okay a very small car and i would walk
up to the car and from here from my
car to that one i would forget why i
stopped just immediately i would just
walk up and go hey
how's it going hey um do you know why i
stopped here
you want to take a stab at it or
anything or
just a wild guess
terrible so i do work uh my full-time
job is actually for the federal
government
thanks
it's a lot of fun we live in the
northern virginia dc area town called
falls church anybody familiar with
foster
yeah that's uh
it's nice we bought a house there for a
very small house from the 1950s great
deal 3 million
and i'm just a lovely
bungalow and the thing is northern
virginia and dc area like any expensive
room they sell you a house they don't
really know what to tell you they just
know it's very expensive and ugly
you know look this one's close to the
metro it's um
six miles you can walk
they never know how to sell expensive
houses in the dc area
this one has a kitchen
there's a bathroom but it's not attached
you have to go outside it used to cost
11 million now it's 13. um
do you want it
after a while i gotta wrap it up but um
so i was living in sunny san diego for a
couple of years anybody in san diego in
san diegoans
yeah beautiful city loved living there
and i had an amazing opportunity
to do comedy in las vegas i was excited
my first comedy gig in las vegas i was
so excited
and the booker said my hair here's the
thing you got to be here tomorrow you
got to be a quick because we need to
we're showing
somebody dropped out please come in i
said okay no problem i was going to
drive but it's like five and a half
hours
so i decided i would fly i'm just like
you know i was on a whim it's like i'm a
comedian i got to do this
so i get online i make a huge mistake
i booked uh spirit has anyone done that
yet does it fly here
does it fly here spirit to salt lake i
took spirit now for those of you who
aren't familiar with it the ticket
was 19 dollars
the bag was 142. i don't understand
how the bag has first class doesn't make
any sense
so i get to the airport it's this giant
yellow plane it's like sitting like this
and it takes like a deep breath it was
like
like it looks sad
the next thing is the plane didn't
actually take off
a giant man came out and picked us up
and just threw us to las vegas
and we just
i love getting on airplanes
early and watching people get on the
airplane
have you ever noticed you're the only
attractive person in that flight
you're the only reasonable you're the
only one that took a shower that morning
have you ever noticed that
and people that like okay the other day
my seat said f5 all right here it is f5
i sat down
some people walk in like they have no
concept of the alphabet
or the order 1 to 26 they just come in
and just
[Laughter]
do we sit on the floor like what no
people that turn around and walk the
other way like where are they going i
forgot
something like what
i get on this spirit flight i'm way
in the back row seven
i get on this spirit flight literally my
seat is a loose stool
that was my seat it was one of these
planes where it had a row of two and
then a row of one
you know which is just really smart
because now you're just sitting there in
an island by yourself
you've got somehow you simultaneously
have the window seat and the aisle it's
really nice
i get on this plane uh mistake number
one is i dropped my phone have you ever
dropped your phone on a plane it's
impossible to retrieve it
physically your body cannot contort to
that position
once you drop your phone you just go and
everybody knows it because they hear
this i hear that
and everybody looks was not mine was
that mine you can
i have dislocated ribs and shoulders
to get because i have to read that text
so bad just
this and just barely i have laid down on
the floor to
just reach which is not good when your
middle eastern on a plane
and i have reached just
terrible idea
i get on this plane normal coach
flight is like this right it's about
like that is that fair
this is economy plus this is coach
this was spirit this is
this guy was so close to me
he kissed me twice it's vegas nobody
cares he just
he kissed me so then i'm flossing his
teeth the whole flight
then he backs up now it's you know and
then the other thing about spirit is
they don't give you free water
they don't they if you if you want water
and you pay for it they just come around
with a spray bottle and they go
there you go sir open your mouth it's
terrible
now here's the only good thing about
spirit okay
a terrorist could not take spirit
because he couldn't get out of his seat
okay listen to me
listen to me where's my phone hang on
hang on
never mind
thank you thank you
last couple of minutes here i'll tell
you a story a very sad story
i was born uh in a large catholic family
and then raised in a southern baptist
home
which makes me incredibly confused
frankly but
we got baptized in lebanon as babies
and then we moved to the south my mom
insisted on getting baptized
now let me stop there and tell you the
middle eastern society culture
um isn't really swimmers
we don't jump in the water necessarily
we go to the beach we go nuts
but we have our shoes on which is weird
but
the this is my beach wear actually but
[Music]
there's no lebanese dive team you know
the olympics just standing there looking
in the water just
i cannot just too deep sorry game over
my mom insisted on getting baptized she
insists massive church everybody's
watching it's a big day for her
excited for her and they got the pool
you know my mom comes down
all right she's she's walking like this
like a man on the moon she's like oh my
gosh and she's speaking in arabic which
is scary
and she's going like this she gets to
the middle
okay normal person gets baptized they go
bloop
and they're done and they go around you
know it's quick and your body your body
bends and then
my my mom for some reason
went like this like her whole body she
was like titanic
reversed she kind of went like this just
completely flat
and the preacher didn't know what to do
she just goes all right
how long should i hold her down there i
don't know
hey man i guess she comes up there's
makeup and arabic everywhere it's just
[Music]
she's she i mean to be quite honest with
you i don't think it worked but um
but um
and the weird thing is like it's hard to
get baptized in a life jacket but
it's um hey guys my name is thank you so
much for coming out appreciate it thank
you
[Applause]